<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:25:25 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:25:25 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are a few of my projects:&#xA;Exploratory Data Analysis Project Demonstrates expertise in exploratory data analysis by extracting, cleaning, and analysing a loan approvals dataset from a Finance Company. Encompasses extraction of data from an RDS database using SQLAlchemy, then cleaning and transformation using Pandas, before conducting exploratory data analysis (EDA) to answer business questions supported by data visualisations and reports.&#xA;View Project: https://github.com/hameed0380/EDA-Customer-Loans&#xA;Multinational Retail Data Centralisation Comprehensive project aimed at transforming and analysing large datasets from multiple data sources.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2024 23:18:54 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>AI, Data Analysis and Engineering Here is some information about me&#xA;A recent graduate in computer science with a specialization in artificial intelligence, I have always been intrigued by AI through activities such as playing AI-based games and watching series like &amp;ldquo;Scorpion.&amp;rdquo; I believe that the advancement of AI and its utilization are pivotal for the improvement of society. Even now, remarkable advancements in AI are evident, and I am eager to contribute to its progress.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
